The next keyword we will look at allows us to
return records between two numbers or two dates.
The actual keyword is the BETWEEN
keyword. For this example,
I want this query to return orders from June 2014.
To accomplish this, I will add a WHERE clause
to the end of this query. Then, I will add the
following: OrderDate BETWEEN '06/01/2014' and
'06/30/2014'. I will add single quotes around
the dates since they have slashes in them.
Otherwise, SQL will think you are trying to do a
division problem. I will run this, and we now see
orders between those two dates. There is one
real-life situation I want to point out here:
This date format assumes 12 AM. If the date field
you are using keeps track of time, you will want
to reflect that in any date criteria. For example,
if we saw that these dates had timestamps,
we would want to change the end date to reflect
11:59:00 PM, as I am doing with this criterion.
Otherwise, you will not see any orders on
June 30 unless they were placed at midnight.
That said, the BETWEEN keyword is inclusive
with a number range or date range,
as we do have orders from
June 30 in this result set.